[
    {
        "question": "Decode the emojis: 🐻🤗. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ✅",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🧠"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bear hug. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🙌",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😔"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 👻📖. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🧠",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ☑️"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: ghost story. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🎉",
            "Nope, I didn’t. ❌"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🥼🐀. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ☑️",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🙌"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: lab rat. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🎊",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😫"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 👨‍🍳📘. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🙌",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🤘"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: cookbook. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🎈",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 🙅"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🥚🐚. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🤘",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ✅"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: eggshell. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🎆",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 🙍"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🍫🥛. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ✅",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🙏"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: chocolate milk. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 💃",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😦"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ⭐️🐟. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🙏",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 👌"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: starfish. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🥳",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😭"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🦀🍰. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 👌",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ☑️"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: crab cake. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😇",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 👿"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🍬🦷. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ☑️",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! ☑️"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: sweet tooth. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 💯",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😩"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: ⛱️🧙‍♀️. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! ✅",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 😼"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: sandwich. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 💅",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 👎"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🗝️🕳️. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 😼",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🥰"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: keyhole. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😺",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😾"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 💪🪑. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🥰",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 👌"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: armchair. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! ❤️",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 💔"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🎂🎁. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 👌",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 👍"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: birthday present. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😘",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😵"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🛏️🐛. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🙆",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 😎"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bedbug. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🌹",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 🥀"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🥵🐕. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 😎",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🙌"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: hot dog. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😙",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 🤕"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🗿📜✂️. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🙌",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 😃"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: rock paper scissors. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😝",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😕"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🍦☀️📅. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 😃",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🧠"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: ice cream sundae. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 😄",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😰"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🔵🐤. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🧠",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 👍"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: bluebird. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 🧠",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 😰"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🖍️🌉. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 👍",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🙆"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: drawbridge. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 👍",
            "Nope, I didn’t. 👎"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Next combo: 🚶🔛☀️. Are you ready?",
        "ans": [
            "Yes, totally! 👍",
            "I guess so. Show me the next puzzle! 🤔"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Answer: walking on sunshine. Did you get it right?",
        "ans": [
            "I sure did! 🌤️",
            "Nope, I didn’t. ⛈️"
        ]
    }
]